And I wish I knew that the doctors
weren't going to help me.
Okay, so if we're people listening, can you
give us three things that you wish
you knew when you first saw your
first bullseye rash?
If you can think of just many, just a few
things that someone can take away from
this, if they find a tick on them, three
things that you wish you knew in the
moment, I wish I knew that I
could get that sick.
I wish I knew that my daughter could be born
with it or my children, and you can
give it through breast milk. And I wish I knew
that the doctors weren't going to
help me. I wish I knew I had more faith in
myself to believe in myself
and not, you know, we've been told our whole
lives that doctors know everything.
Oh, they're the smartest, but they
don't know everything.